{
  "type": "flashcards",
  "language_code": "ja",
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "ア",
      "answer": "a"
    },
    {
      "question": "エ",
      "answer": "e"
    },
    {
      "question": "カ",
      "answer": "ka"
    },
    {
      "question": "イ",
      "answer": "i"
    },
    {
      "question": "ウ",
      "answer": "u"
    },
    {
      "question": "オ",
      "answer": "o"
    },
    {
      "question": "ク",
      "answer": "ku"
    },
    {
      "question": "ケ",
      "answer": "ke"
    },
    {
      "question": "コ",
      "answer": "ko"
    },
    {
      "question": "サ",
      "answer": "sa"
    },
    {
      "question": "シ",
      "answer": "shi"
    },
    {
      "question": "ス",
      "answer": "su"
    },
    {
      "question": "セ",
      "answer": "se"
    },
    {
      "question": "ソ",
      "answer": "so"
    },
    {
      "question": "タ",
      "answer": "ta"
    },
    {
      "question": "チ",
      "answer": "chi"
    },
    {
      "question": "ツ",
      "answer": "tsu"
    },
    {
      "question": "テ",
      "answer": "te"
    },
    {
      "question": "ト",
      "answer": "to"
    },
    {
      "question": "ナ",
      "answer": "na"
    },
    {
      "question": "ニ",
      "answer": "ni"
    },
    {
      "question": "ヌ",
      "answer": "nu"
    },
    {
      "question": "ネ",
      "answer": "ne"
    },
    {
      "question": "ノ",
      "answer": "no"
    },
    {
      "question": "ハ",
      "answer": "ha"
    },
    {
      "question": "ヒ",
      "answer": "hi"
    },
    {
      "question": "フ",
      "answer": "fu"
    },
    {
      "question": "ヘ",
      "answer": "he"
    },
    {
      "question": "ホ",
      "answer": "ho"
    },
    {
      "question": "マ",
      "answer": "ma"
    },
    {
      "question": "ミ",
      "answer": "mi"
    },
    {
      "question": "ム",
      "answer": "mu"
    },
    {
      "question": "メ",
      "answer": "me"
    },
    {
      "question": "モ",
      "answer": "mo"
    },
    {
      "question": "ヤ",
      "answer": "ya"
    },
    {
      "question": "ユ",
      "answer": "yu"
    },
    {
      "question": "ヨ",
      "answer": "yo"
    },
    {
      "question": "ラ",
      "answer": "ra"
    },
    {
      "question": "リ",
      "answer": "ri"
    },
    {
      "question": "ル",
      "answer": "ru"
    },
    {
      "question": "レ",
      "answer": "re"
    },
    {
      "question": "ロ",
      "answer": "ro"
    },
    {
      "question": "ワ",
      "answer": "wa"
    },
    {
      "question": "ヲ",
      "answer": "wo"
    },
    {
      "question": "ン",
      "answer": "n"
    },
    {
      "question": "キ",
      "answer": "ki"
    }
  ]
}
